sportsbetting.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy—Online Sports Betting, Online Sportsbook, Racebook Betting, Casino & Poker

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices of Interactive Systems Inc d/b/a SPORTSBETTING.COM.

SPORTSBETTING.COM would like to build your trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy we have agreed to notify you of the following.

If you feel that we are not abiding by our posted privacy policy, you should contact us by filling out this form.

* ### Information Collection and Use

Interactive Systems Inc is the sole owner of the information collected on this website. We will not share or rent this information with others in ways different than indicated in this statement, except we reserve the right to sell or share this information with a third party for the purpose of continuing to provide you the wagering and contest services found on our website. We collect information from you at several different points on our website.

* ### Registration

In order to gain membership to our site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give your contact information (such as name, address, phone number and e-mail address). This information is used to contact you about the services on our site, to mail you CD ROM software and to mail you checks for your winnings.

* ### Placing Wagers

In order to place a wager with us you must give us and our third party financial services processors your financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to return your winnings to you.

* ### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Usage of a cookie is not linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If you reject the cookie, you may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that you will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, you may not be able to participate in our sweepstakes or contests. Cookies also enable us to track and target your interests to enhance your experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example certain contest promoters). However, we do not have access to nor do we control these cookies.

* #### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

* #### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We use an outside shipping company to ship our CD ROM's, an outside hosting company to host our mailing lists and a third party financial processing company to process deposits and withdrawals into and out of your account. These companies do not use your personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

We may, from time to time, partner with another party to provide specific services. If you sign up for these services, we may share your name or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services to you.

These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

* ### Links

This web site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

* ### Newsletter

All members of or our site and all contest entrants are automatically subscribed to our monthly newsletter. If you wish to unsubscribe from our newsletter you may do this at any time by following the simple instructions at the bottom of the newsletter. 

* #### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site may request information from you via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code and age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. All contest entrants will automatically be subscribed to our monthly newsletter. 

* ### Refer a Friend

If you elect to use our referral service to inform a friend about our site, we ask for your friend's name and e-mail address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit this site. We do not store this information permanently.

* ### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via this website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration and financial processing forms ask you to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or birth date), that information is encrypted and protected with the best encryption software in the industry - 128 bit SSL. While on a secure page such as our credit card form, the lock icon on the bottom of your web browser becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link [http://www.ssl.com](http://www.ssl.com/).

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect your information off-line. Your information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

* #### Site and Service Updates

We also may send you site and service announcement updates. You are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We may communicate with you via e-mail or phone to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to your account.

* #### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information (such as your e-mail address) changes, or if you no longer desire our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove your personal data provided to us. This can usually be done by [contacting our customer service department via Live Chat](http://server.iad.liveperson.net/hc/13561672/?cmd=file&file=visitorWantsToChat&site=13561672&byhref=1&imageUrl=http://server.iad.liveperson.net/hcp/Gallery/ChatButton-Gallery/English/General/1a), or calling them toll-free - North America: 1-866-395-1043 , UK: (0) 800-008-7612. Changes to your e-mail address and physical address should also be sent to us using this form, if you wish to continue to receive our newsletter and our free CD ROM software.

* #### Not Accessible by Minors

We provide services to adults only. Persons under the age of 18 are not permitted to use our services. 

* #### Choice/Opt-out

You are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your information used for purposes such as newsletters and special offers by following the simple instructions at the bottom of any one of these documents that are sent to you. 

We will strive to inform you when your information is being collected by outside parties. We do this so you can make an informed decision as to whether you should proceed with services that we offer through an outside party.

* #### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on our site so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated in this statement, we will notify you by way of an e-mail. You will have a choice as to whether or not to allow us to use your information in this different manner.
